Veronika Romaniuk

Berlin, Germany Teleg., Wats.: +380968553515 Mobile: +4915158845261 ver.romaniuk@gmail.com

Profile

Born in Kyiv, Ukraine, I attended Kyiv International School, from which I applied to New York University in New York. I graduated, having studied Psychology, Social Sciences, and Cinema. After graduation I pursued the sharing of content through exhibitions, project-based freelance editing for creative writing, and copywriting and SMM in a marketing position.

Skills

- ❖ Languages: fluent English, Ukrainian, Russian, intermediate German, beginner French;
- Experienced in: copywriting, graphic design, filmmaking and montage, SMM Instagram, Pinterest;
- ❖ Visual design: Figma, Adobe Photoshop, p5.js, Resolume Arena;
- ❖ Data analysis: Microsoft Excel.

Education

2018 – 2022 New York University

New York City, USA BA Independent Study

• GPA: 3.93

• Minor in Psychology

• Courses on p5.js, Maya, Unity.

05.2021 – 08.2021 Kyiv Academy of Media Arts

Kyiv, Ukraine New Media

• Education on TouchDesigner, Resolume Arena;

2005 – 2018 Kyiv International School

Kyiv, Ukraine

• GPA: 3.91.

Work Experience

08.23 – 11.2023 Marketing, SMM

Kim Kimchi Kyiv, Ukraine

Photography, video montage, content creation for marketing of restaurant

chain, managing Pinterest page.

07.2022 – 11.2022 Curator, Event Manager, Promotional Content Creator

Wild Corners Berlin, Germany

Putting together exhibitions in support of the Kinburn Spit, Ukraine, which is occupied and catching fire due to shelling. Experience creating a digital identity, promotional material, event organizing; exhibition on July 14th and

August 6th.

06.2022 New Media Instructor

Young Arts Neukölln Berlin, Germany

Organizing a series of workshops with Ukrainian children on 3D scanning – sculpting and fashion for representation in virtual 3D spaces, preparation of exhibition.

04.2022 – 07.2022 Volunteer Virtual Gallery Designer, Graphic Designer

Vitsche Ukrainian Culture Station

Berlin, Germany

Creation of a 3D virtual gallery space for representation of Ukrainian artists, preparation of exhibition, promotional material design.

07.2021 - 08.2021 Volunteer at camp and resort

Authentic Camp

Kinburn Split, Ukraine

Visual design of promotional material, decoration of physical space.

11.2020 – 01.2021 Studio Manager

DJ School & Studio Kultura Zvuka

Kiev, Ukraine

Managing the lesson schedule and caring for the studio space.

10.2020 – 01.2021 Intern Photographer and Paid Copywriter

Architecture Firm Balbek Buro

Kiev, Ukraine

Photography of ongoing and completed projects, writing of descriptive

project reports.

05.2019 – 07.2019 Photographer, Copywriter, Graphic Designer

Save The Children Amman, Jordan

Photographing events, creating visual info-graphics.

06.2018 – 08.2018 Graphic Designer

IOS and Android startup 'Quests' Kiev, Ukraine Visual app design in Figma.